Double Daddy is a thriller, drama, tv movie film directed by Lee Friedlander.
A teen's life turns upside down when her boyfriend
impregnates both her and a new student at school.
Amanda, played by Mollee Gray.
Heather, played by Brittany Curran.
Connor, played by Cameron Palatas.
Diane, played by Maeve Quinlan.
Trish, played by René Ashton.
Jeff, played by Boyd Kestner.
Daddy's Double is a 1910 American silent short drama
produced by the Thanhouser Film Corporation.
The film focuses on Hal, a young man, who proposes to Sue, his love interest.
Her father overhears and becomes furious before whisking
his daughter away to a boarding school.
Hal and Sue attempt to elope, but it is foiled.
Hal then gets an idea to disguise himself as the father and reclaim Sue.
The plan works, but the father follows in pursuit.
He breaks into the wedding ceremony at the parson's house and sees his double.
He then laughs and approves of the marriage.
The film was the fourth release by Thanhouser and it was
met with favorable reviews by critics.
In 2007, a surviving print was released on DVD with a new
original score composed and performed by Raymond A.
The film explores themes of baby, teen movie, pregnant
woman, woman director, teen pregnancy.
The tone is emotional and intense.